<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News | Chain Games</title>
	<atom:link href="./index.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../../index.html</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 19:42:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Chain Games Partners with Centralex Announcing Token Listing and Airdrop of CENX Tokens to Existing CHAIN Stakers</title>
		<link>./../../../chain-games-partners-with-centralex-announcing-token-listing-and-airdrop-of-cenx-tokens-to-existing-chain-stakers/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 19:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exchanges]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchanges]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[news]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=3191</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tallinn, Estonia&#8211; (Chain Games OU. – May 14th, 2021) &#8211;  Chain Games, OU, a blockchain gaming and Esports company, is pleased to announce a partnership with Centralex Exchange, resulting in a token listing of the Company’s CHAIN gaming token, as well as an airdrop of CENX tokens to all existing CHAIN stakers.    With the Centralex [&#8230;]</p>
The post <a href="./../../../chain-games-partners-with-centralex-announcing-token-listing-and-airdrop-of-cenx-tokens-to-existing-chain-stakers/index.html">Chain Games Partners with Centralex Announcing Token Listing and Airdrop of CENX Tokens to Existing CHAIN Stakers</a> first appeared on <a href="./../../../index.html">Chain Games</a>.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tallinn, Estonia&#8211; (Chain Games OU. – May 14th, 2021) &#8211;  Chain Games, OU, a blockchain gaming and Esports company, is pleased to announce a partnership with Centralex Exchange, resulting in a token listing of the Company’s CHAIN gaming token, as well as an airdrop of CENX tokens to all existing CHAIN stakers.   </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With the Centralex partnership, Chain Games’ players will be able to conveniently exchange fiat and crypto for CHAIN tokens for the purposes of playing games, thereby expanding the Company’s crypto and fiat footprint. Players will be able to buy and sell CHAIN tokens directly on the Centralex exchange platform using crypto, bank transfers or bank cards, and with on-ramp methods including Visa, Mastercard, SEPA and more. The partnership improves the accessibility of crypto to savvy and novice players helping accelerate wider adoption of Chain Games’ online Esports platform.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">In addition to the Centralex listing, all current CHAIN stakers as of May 17th, 11:59:59PM UTC, will receive a weighted airdrop of CENX tokens equivalent to 2% of the total CENX supply.  The date of the airdrop will commence one week after the listing of the CHAIN token on the Centralex Exchange platform.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chain Games’ CEO, Adam Barlam explains that &#8220;One of the biggest user pain points in blockchain gaming and crypto in general, is buying CHAIN tokens or any tokens with fiat or crypto, and Centralex helps reduce the barriers for global competitive gamers.  Crypto and fiat on and off-ramps will play an important role in the scaling and adoption of our gaming platform, and the partnership with Centralex will help us to generate broader access to various players with differing familiarity with crypto.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Centralex CEO, Tristan Roozendaal explains that &#8220;We at Centralex have a very strong foundation of ex-bankers and crypto fanatics. Centralex is a fully regulated Estonian exchange, and uses the latest wallet technologies to safeguard clients&#8217; funds via “FireBlocks”, our wallet service provider offering Custo-DeFi solutions.  We are excited to extend this functionality to the Chain Games community and new and existing token holders and gamers!&#8221; </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">About Centralex</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Centralex is an international fully regulated Estonian cryptocurrency exchange . With a global vision in mind and an international office footprint spanning two continents, Centralex strives to bring remarkable people together to do extraordinary things.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To contact Centralex:</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Website: </span><a href="https://centralex.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://centralex.com/</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">Twitter: </span><a href="https://twitter.com/CentraleX_hk"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/CentraleX_hk</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">Telegram: </span><a href="https://t.me/centralexhk"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://t.me/centralexhk</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">Email: </span><a href="mailto:media@centralex.io"><span style="font-weight: 400;">media@centralex.io</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">About Chain Games</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chain Games is a blockchain enabled gaming platform designed to allow competitive Esports competitions on a non-custodial, decentralized platform governed by an Ethereum Smart Contract.  </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To contact Chain Games:</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Website: </span><a href="./../../../index.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">./../../../index.html</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">Twitter: </span><a href="https://twitter.com/realchaingames"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/realchaingames</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">Telegram: </span><a href="https://t.me/chaingames"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://t.me/chaingames</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">Email: </span><a href="mailto:brian@chaingames.io"><span style="font-weight: 400;">brian@chaingames.io</span></a></p>The post <a href="./../../../chain-games-partners-with-centralex-announcing-token-listing-and-airdrop-of-cenx-tokens-to-existing-chain-stakers/index.html">Chain Games Partners with Centralex Announcing Token Listing and Airdrop of CENX Tokens to Existing CHAIN Stakers</a> first appeared on <a href="./../../../index.html">Chain Games</a>.]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chain Games Partners with Transak to Power Fiat-Crypto Blockchain Gaming Gateway </title>
		<link>./../../../chain-games-partners-with-transak-to-power-fiat-crypto-blockchain-gaming-gateway/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 19:55:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[blockchain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chain games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[esports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fiat]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gaming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[transak]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=3183</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tallinn, Estonia and Boulder, Colorado&#8211;(Chain Games OU – May 10th, 2021) &#8211;  Chain Games, OU, a blockchain gaming and Esports company, is pleased to announce that the Company has partnered with Transak to power its gaming platform. With the Transak partnership, Chain Games’ players will be able to conveniently use fiat to purchase CHAIN tokens [&#8230;]</p>
The post <a href="./../../../chain-games-partners-with-transak-to-power-fiat-crypto-blockchain-gaming-gateway/index.html">Chain Games Partners with Transak to Power Fiat-Crypto Blockchain Gaming Gateway </a> first appeared on <a href="./../../../index.html">Chain Games</a>.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tallinn, Estonia and Boulder, Colorado&#8211;(Chain Games OU – May 10th, 2021) &#8211;  Chain Games, OU, a blockchain gaming and Esports company, is pleased to announce that the Company has partnered with Transak to power its gaming platform.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With the Transak partnership, Chain Games’ players will be able to conveniently use fiat to purchase CHAIN tokens for the purposes of playing games thereby expanding the Company’s crypto footprint in more than 60 countries worldwide. Players will be able to buy CHAIN tokens directly using a bank transfer or bank card with payment methods including Visa, Mastercard, SEPA and more. The partnership improves the accessibility of crypto to savvy and novice players helping accelerate wider adoption of Chain Games’ online Esports platform.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chain Games’ CEO, Adam Barlam explains that &#8220;one of the biggest user pain points in blockchain gaming and crypto in general, is buying CHAIN tokens or any tokens with fiat, and Transak helps reduce the barriers for global competitive gamers.  Fiat on-ramps will play an important role in the scaling and adoption of our gaming platform and the partnership with Transak will help us to generate broader access to various players with differing familiarity with crypto.”</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Transak CEO, Sami Start explains that &#8220;Transak is on a mission to make it easier to connect money and data to your blockchain wallet. We believe that the blockchain wallet will become a single sign-on for finance. Kind of like sign in with Google or Facebook, but with way more features. We are very pleased to partner with Chain Games to help grow the adoption of the Chain Games platform.&#8221; </span></p>
<p><strong>About Transak</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Transak is a single integration for applications to accept fiat-to-crypto deposits and withdrawals from a global user base. It does this by aggregating fiat on-ramps from around the world and abstracting away the complexity of local compliance, payment methods, and operations. Transak is backed by Consensys. For more information, please visit </span><a href="https://www.newsfilecorp.com/redirect/gppOUMjEm"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://transak.com/</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span></p>
<p><strong>About Chain Games</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chain Games is a blockchain enabled gaming platform designed to allow competitive Esports competitions on a non-custodial, decentralized platform governed by an Ethereum Smart Contract.  </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To contact Chain Games:</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Website: </span><a href="./../../../index.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">./../../../index.html</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">Twitter: </span><a href="https://twitter.com/realchaingames"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://twitter.com/realchaingames</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">Telegram: </span><a href="https://t.me/chaingames"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://t.me/chaingames</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">Email: </span><a href="mailto:brian@chaingames.io"><span style="font-weight: 400;">brian@chaingames.io</span></a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"></p>
<p></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>The post <a href="./../../../chain-games-partners-with-transak-to-power-fiat-crypto-blockchain-gaming-gateway/index.html">Chain Games Partners with Transak to Power Fiat-Crypto Blockchain Gaming Gateway </a> first appeared on <a href="./../../../index.html">Chain Games</a>.]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chain Games First 40 Days Recap:  A Message from the CEO</title>
		<link>./../../../chain-games-first-40-days-recap-a-message-from-the-ceo/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 08:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[updates]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dev.chaingames.io/?p=2955</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hey Chain Gang!  For only being around for just under 40 days, we have made incredible strides in such a short period of time! August 24th marked the launch of our first fully working product and proof of concept use case Super Crypto Kart for Windows, Mac OS and Linux.  We had great feedback and [&#8230;]</p>
The post <a href="./../../../chain-games-first-40-days-recap-a-message-from-the-ceo/index.html">Chain Games First 40 Days Recap:  A Message from the CEO</a> first appeared on <a href="./../../../index.html">Chain Games</a>.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Hey Chain Gang!  For only being around for just under 40 days, we have made incredible strides in such a short period of time!</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><b>August 24th</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> marked the launch of our first fully working product and proof of concept use case Super Crypto Kart for Windows, Mac OS and Linux.  We had great feedback and users really loved the concept and game with hundreds of downloads just on Day 1!</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">On </span><b>August 26th</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> we launched our much anticipated ILO on Uniswap and were the 3rd most traded token on the DEX beating out several stable coins and trading nearly 20M USD in volume!  Quite the feat for a new token!</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Layer 1 multiplayer launched shortly thereafter amidst the DeFi craze of August and early September.  We quickly realized that with the escalating GAS fees on the Ethereum network that we needed to take action and FAST!</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">We started working on a Layer 2 solution on the MATIC network on </span><b>September 16th</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">, and just </span><b>7 days later</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> had a fully working version of Super Crypto Kart and ported the Chain Games network to be able to run on MATIC testnet.  </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">One day after our testnet launch on </span><b>September 24th</b><span style="font-weight: 400;">, we released the full version of multiplayer on Layer 2 MATIC mainnet!  We had amazing execution and commitment from our dev team and support from all members of the community to push out this full stack solution in such record time!  8 days is truly an incredible timeframe to complete such a task, especially in the crypto world. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">With Layer 2 running optimally, we were able to reduce GAS fees to next to nothing, while significantly increasing game speed, contract execution time, and improving UX.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">On </span><b>September 27th</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> we announced our intention to implement Call of Duty: Modern Warfare where users can compete on Battle Royale style matches and multiplayer battles for most points, kills, wins, and more to win $CHAIN!  In addition we are researching other Tier 1 games where we can execute this same method.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><b><img loading="lazy" class="alignleft wp-image-2278 size-full" src="./../../../wp-content/uploads/2020/10/atari-mention.jpg" alt="" width="250" height="141" />October 2nd</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> marked the news of a MASSIVE strategic partnership with one of the world’s most iconic consumer brands and interactive entertainment producers, ATARI.  ATARI will be integrating the $CHAIN token into their soon to be launched ATARI Crypto-casino, and Chain Games will be implementing the ATRI token into the CHAIN ecosystem.  Furthermore, ATARI CEO Fred Chesnais has accepted an advisory role on the Chain Games board!  This partnership closely aligns both companies continued interests in blockchain, crypto and the video game industry moving forward.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">On </span><b>October 4th </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">we</span> <span style="font-weight: 400;">released the much anticipated Super Crypto Kart for Android with full single player and online multiplayer modes enabled!  This enables cross-platform play across Windows, Mac OS, Linux and now Android!  iOS is next!</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><b>October 5th </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">we announced that our Call of Duty: Modern Warfare implementation will be completed and launched towards the end of November.  Not only that, but we have also started working on adding top tier games </span><b>Fortnite, Madden 21, FIFA 21 </b><span style="font-weight: 400;">and</span><b> Fall Guys</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to the list of playable games to compete on in the Chain Games network!  The competition is going to get fierce, and so are the $CHAIN payouts for winners!</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">It has been a very productive 40 days Chain Gang, and we anticipate the next 40 days to be just as productive as we go full steam into releasing high profile games to play on the Chain network.  We feel these new tier 1 games will really draw in the audience we need and expect to continue down the path of blockchain gaming excellence!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Until next time,</span></p>
<p><em><span style="font-weight: 400;">Adam Barlam</span></em><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">CEO / Founder Chain Games </span></p>The post <a href="./../../../chain-games-first-40-days-recap-a-message-from-the-ceo/index.html">Chain Games First 40 Days Recap:  A Message from the CEO</a> first appeared on <a href="./../../../index.html">Chain Games</a>.]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Atari® Teams Up with Chain Games to Integrate Atari Token Into Chain Games Ecosystem</title>
		<link>./../../../atari-teams-up-with-chain-games-to-integrate-atari-token-into-chain-games-ecosystem/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 08:28:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[atari]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[news]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dev.chaingames.io/?p=2952</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Atari CEO Frederic Chesnais to Serve as Advisor for Chain Games as Companies Integrate One Another’s Cryptocurrencies into Their Respective Interactive Entertainment Offerings Both Groups also did proceed with a Token Swap, subject to lockup &#160; New York, NY (October 2nd, 2020) –  Atari® — one of the world’s most iconic consumer brands and entertainment [&#8230;]</p>
The post <a href="./../../../atari-teams-up-with-chain-games-to-integrate-atari-token-into-chain-games-ecosystem/index.html">Atari® Teams Up with Chain Games to Integrate Atari Token Into Chain Games Ecosystem</a> first appeared on <a href="./../../../index.html">Chain Games</a>.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Atari CEO Frederic Chesnais to Serve as Advisor for Chain Games as Companies Integrate One Another’s Cryptocurrencies into Their Respective Interactive Entertainment Offerings</span></i></p>
<p><i>Both Groups also did proceed with a Token Swap, subject to lockup</i></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><b>New York</b><b>, NY (</b><b>October 2nd, 2020)</b><span style="font-weight: 400;"> –  </span><a href="https://www.atari.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Atari®</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> — one of the world’s most iconic consumer brands and entertainment producers — today announced a partnership with gaming ecosystem, Chain Games. The terms of the collaboration include the integration of the Atari Token (ATRI) as a support cryptocurrency in Chain Games’ first-party blockchain-based titles — starting with </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Super Crypto Kart</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> — as well as Chain’s upcoming marketplace and fantasy sports platform. Atari will additionally support the CHAIN Token ($CHAIN) across its library of future </span><a href="https://casinoatari.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Atari Crypto Casino</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> titles. </span></p>
<p>Chain Games<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.0.1/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />(chaingames.io) is an evolution in Web 3.0 blockchain gaming, combining smart contract-based contests with state of the art gameplay. Committed to transitioning the blockchain gaming industry into the modern gaming era, the Chain Games’s ecosystem fits into three core categories: the development of first-party proprietary games featuring live multiplayer and crypto payouts; an open Chain dApp Game Store where developers can integrate Chain Games’ SmartContests<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.0.1/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> system into their games; and collaboration with established game studios to integrate Chain Games’ systems and CHAIN Token into their titles.</p>
<p>Chain Games’ products are fully ERC-20 and Ethereum compatible. SmartContests<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.0.1/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> is an industry first contract-based competition system where players can compete in games of skill to earn winnings. SmartStaking<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.0.1/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Gaming Contracts reward stakers on the network with 15% of the fees generated on each game played, allowing them to passively earn on any game played on the Chain network. <i>Super Crypto Kart</i> is the first blockchain-integrated game to utilize the Chain Games SmartContests<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.0.1/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Gaming Contracts. Super Crypto Kart is a cross platform kart-<span style="font-weight: 400;">based racing game that is currently available on Windows, Mac OS, Linux, and soon to be released on Android, and iOS.</span></p>
<p>Both companies have swapped tokens for the equivalent of $200,000, subject to a 6-month lockup.</p>
<p>“We are pleased to announce today a strategic partnership with Chain Games, a true pioneer in blockchain-based gaming,” said Fred Chesnais, CEO of Atari. “The technologies which power the Chain Games network create exciting and new possibilities for developers and users, ensuring secure transitions, financial versatility, and additional sources of revenue not just for game makers — but also for players interested in raising the stakes of competitive multiplayer experiences.”</p>
<p>“Atari is one of the most recognized consumer brands in the video game and entertainment space and we are ecstatic to be part of the Atari family,” said Adam Barlam, CEO &amp; Founder of Chain Games.</p>
<p>Atari Chain CEO Frédéric Chesnais will also advise the Chain Games Board of Directors.</p>
<p>Atari Chain Ltd. is a subsidiary of Atari SA, created to lead the development of ongoing projects in the field of cryptocurrencies in entertainment-based industries. The Atari Token, currently slated to be listed in November of 2020, is issued by Atari Chain, Ltd (Gibraltar), a company equally owned by Atari and the ICICB Group.</p>
<p>For more information on Atari Chain, please join the Atari Telegram at <a href="https://pr.report/W0nYN3Lq">https://t.me/AtariTokenOfficial</a> and visit <a href="https://pr.report/KZdbyDJN">atarichain.com</a>.</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">To stay up-to-date on all things Atari and retro-pop-culture, follow on </span><a href="http://www.facebook.com/Atari"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Facebook</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, </span><a href="http://www.twitter.com/atari"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Twitter</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, and </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/atari/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Instagram</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<p><b><br />
About Atari </b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Atari® is an interactive entertainment company. As an iconic brand that transcends generations and audiences, the company is globally recognized for its multi-platform, interactive entertainment, and licensed products. Atari owns and/or manages a portfolio of more than 200 games and franchises, including world-renowned brands like </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Asteroids®, Centipede®, Missile Command®, Pong®,</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and </span><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">RollerCoaster Tycoon®</span></i><span style="font-weight: 400;">. Atari has offices in New York and Paris. Visit us online at</span><a href="http://www.atari.com/"><span style="font-weight: 400;"> www.atari.com</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<p><b><br />
About Chain Games</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chain Games</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.0.1/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></span><span style="font-weight: 400;">is an evolution in Web 3.0 blockchain gaming combining smart contract based contests with state of the art gameplay.  Chain Games is committed to transitioning the blockchain gaming industry into the modern gaming era. Chain Games is an Estonian Private Limited Liability Company. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">For more information on Chain Games, please join the Chain Games Telegram at </span><a href="https://t.me/chaingames"><span style="font-weight: 400;">https://t.me/chaingames</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and visit </span><a href="./../../../index.html"><span style="font-weight: 400;">./../../../index.html</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">To stay up-to-date on all things Chain Games, follow on </span><a href="https://twitter.com/realchaingames"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Twitter</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and </span><a href="https://www.facebook.com/realchaingames"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Facebook</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">.</span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">###</span></p>
<p><b>Press Contacts:</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"> </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For Atari:<br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">UberStrategist Inc.<br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Mario R. Kroll and CJ Melendez<br />
</span><a href="https://pr.report/1Vlk8tYs">pr@uberstrategist.com</a><br />
<span style="font-weight: 400;">646-844-8388</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
For Chain Games:<br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Chain Games OÜ<br />
</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sundeep S.</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"><br />
</span><a href="mailto:outreach@chaingames.io"><span style="font-weight: 400;">outreach@chaingames.io</span></a><span id="more-2952"></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>The post <a href="./../../../atari-teams-up-with-chain-games-to-integrate-atari-token-into-chain-games-ecosystem/index.html">Atari® Teams Up with Chain Games to Integrate Atari Token Into Chain Games Ecosystem</a> first appeared on <a href="./../../../index.html">Chain Games</a>.]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
